Satya and Jane from Bank of America. Please go ahead. Hi there. Thanks for my question. So I am
going to ask a question that's very tight and given there's a lot of focus, it's a kind of
catch-all question. So given the change from your communication in and out of analimab
showrooms on clinically meaningful, just wondering whether you've decided internally how you define
clinically meaningful for three reads, investors most focus on, so Pella, Remy, MSDM1. Maybe just
give you a catch-all. Is it fair to think that any static benefit is clinically meaningful in
your eyes for different reasons for each asset and any changes in level of confidence on each?
Thanks a lot. Yeah, thanks, Satya. So no,
no,
no change from previous comments. We don't know anything else that I can provide on on any of the
three. I think in terms of how we will read them out, I mean, I think we always focus on the on
the primary endpoint and statistical significance and reaching the goal and the primary endpoint in
the study. I think certainly so that I mean, that will guide how we how we communicate and then as
appropriate additional secondary endpoints as well, if appropriate, to comment on them.
I mean, I think for for Pella Farson, as we've guided in the past, we continue to, we powered the study for the kind of 13 to 15% CVR benefit, and certainly are hopeful to see that level or higher. And if we can see higher, obviously, we'd prefer that. But I think that's how we think about it. In MS, we'll certainly be looking at not only the AR reduction, but also the impact on disability and clearly on DM1, in addition to VIA.
Thank you.
also want to see some of the secondary endpoints and how they perform as well. But I think that
the reality is we have to be thoughtful because we want to be able to preserve the ability to
present this data at high profile Congresses in the future. So we'll navigate that best we can,
making sure investors have clarity on what we believe the path forward is, but still preserving
that ability to present the data as well. Can I just say one follow on back? You've
commented when that answers the powering of TELA. I don't think you've ever given us any
color on how Remy MS or DM1 are powered. Yeah, I don't think we have for either of those. I think
for MF, you all know well how studies that are head to head against Obagio have been powered
in the past. So I think that you have that as background. So I don't think there's more that
I could provide, but provide there. And I think on DM1, primary endpoint is VHAT. And then we have